a single pellet can safely store several
hundred meters of a lightweight cable
[Music]
attention all units in the confines of
precinct 13 receiving a 1030 on West
19th Street and Broadway assailant is
Caucasian male mid-30s 170 to 180 pounds
shoulder-length blond hair last seen on
foot heading eastbound on 19th Street
[Music]
got a description well no he was math
mask and most of his victims are
suspects I love them with serious rap
sheets are calling him a vigilant okay
he's not a vigilante
[Music]
and spandex
everything stand extraordinary velocity
vector is a function of both mass and
acceleration oh come on you know better
than anyone the weight of the bobbin any
pendulum has no effect on swing see it
doesn't affect frequency but it's
totally it's actually momentum
[Music]
hey MA yes eggs organic got it
you